<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HFUT</title>
    <link>https://icesuki.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on HFUT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://icesuki.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Code</title>
      <link>https://icesuki.github.io/code/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icesuki.github.io/code/</guid>
      <description>TIOBE Index for December 2021   Rank Language Rating Change     1 Python 12.90% +0.69%   2 C 11.80% -4.69%   3 Java 10.12% -2.41%   4 C++ 7.73% +0.82%   5 C# 6.40% +2.21%   6 Visual Basic 5.40% +1.48%   7 JavaScript 2.30% -0.06%   8 Assembly language 2.25% +0.91%   9 SQL 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Departments set up</title>
      <link>https://icesuki.github.io/posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icesuki.github.io/posts/</guid>
      <description>School of Mechanical Engineering
 Mechanical design and manufacturing and automation
  Industrial engineering
  Aircraft manufacturing Engineering
  Process equipment and control engineering
  Intelligent manufacturing Engineering
   School of Materials Science and Engineering
 Major in Powder Material Science and engineering
  Major in Material Physics
  New energy materials and devices
  Inorganic nonmetallic material engineering major</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hefei University Of Technology</title>
      <link>https://icesuki.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icesuki.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>IntroduceHefei University of Technology is a national key University directly under the Ministry of Education of the People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of China. It is co-established by the Ministry of Education, Anhui Provincial People&amp;rsquo;s Government, Ministry of Industry and Information Technology and State Administration of Science, Technology and Industry for National Defence. Hefei University of Technology is one of the top universities in the world. National &amp;ldquo;211 Project&amp;rdquo; construction university, national &amp;ldquo;985 Project Superior Discipline Innovation Platform&amp;rdquo; construction university; Included in the national &amp;ldquo;2011 project&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;111&amp;rdquo; plan, excellence engineers education program, the national college students&#39; innovative experiment plan, national college students&#39; innovative entrepreneurial training plan, national construction under high level university graduate student projects, new technical research and practice, the national college students&#39; cultural quality education base, the national innovative entrepreneurial base, the national education practice in colleges and universities One of the first demonstration universities for deepening innovation and Entrepreneurship Education reform, universities with typical experience in Innovation and entrepreneurship in China, universities receiving Chinese government scholarship for International students, and member units of CDIO Engineering Education Alliance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Industrial manufacturing network foundation</title>
      <link>https://icesuki.github.io/me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icesuki.github.io/me/</guid>
      <description>Author: XXX KyClass: Intelligent Manufacturing Engineering Class 19-1Student id: 20XXXXX134Phone: 15XXXXXX358QQ: 1XXXXXXXXXXX7</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music Applications</title>
      <link>https://icesuki.github.io/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icesuki.github.io/music/</guid>
      <description>QQ MusicNetEase Cloud MusicKuwo MusicKuGou</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>https://icesuki.github.io/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icesuki.github.io/news/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;System Engineering Theory and Application of Intelligent Interconnected Systems&amp;rdquo;, Project of Basic Science Center of National Natural Science Foundation of China, Hefei University of TechnologyDate: 2021-12-14 Source: Party and Government Office (Development and Planning Office)
 Recently, the basic science Center project of &amp;ldquo;Systems Engineering Theory and Application of Intelligent Interconnected Systems&amp;rdquo; was officially launched by the National Natural Science Foundation of China. The project is led and hosted by Hefei University of Technology, with Tsinghua University and Global Energy Internet Research Institute Co.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
